learningfarm.com 2019-05-31

# 

What information do we collect? 

When creating a school account on Learning Farm, you enter your name, school name, and email address. Student accounts on Learning Farm are created by the school administrator and do not include email addresses or any other personally identifiable information. 

What do we use your information for? 

The school account information we collect is used to verify your status as a US K-12 school and to enable Learning Farm to provide customer support for your use of our program. 

Student information is used for educational or school purposes, and as authorized by a parent or student. Overall, student information is used to improve our systems in order to provide the best possible educational experience for users. 

Following the termination of a license, a school, district, or parent may request that Learning Farm delete or de-identify student information and Learning Farm will do so. 

How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit card data, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

Do we use cookies? 

We do not use cookies. 

Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties any of your information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance (COPPA)

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA)

The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) (20 U.S.C. § 1232g; 34 CFR Part 99) is a Federal law that protects the privacy of student education records. The law applies to all schools that receive funds under an applicable program of the U.S. Department of Education. Should you choose to enter in any information that is considered an educational record protected by the act, then students have the right to expect that those records within Learning Farm will not be viewable by guests and others who are not school officials. 

Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
